

Contact

aaaa8552369@gmail.com

(C) 09 11780380

Education

Bachelor's Degree (2018 ~ 2022)

National Tsing Hua University Power Mechanical Engineering

Master Degree (2022 ~ Now)

National Tsing Hua University Power Mechanical Engineering

Expertise

- Robotics
- Autonomous Mobile Robot
- Embedded System
- ROS Environment
- System Integration
- Deep Learning
- MATLAB Develop

Interest Domain

- Robotics
- Computer Vision
- Self-Driving Car
- Artificial Intelligence

Eric Chiou 邱柏鎧

About Me

During the period of university, I was attracted by the student robotics team DIT and joined them. In this team, I had learned lots of knowledge about mechatronics, also cultivated my practical experience of creating wheeled robots.

Experience

Q 2018.10 - 2019.03

Join ASME SPDC competition

Topic: Robot for warehousing with remote control

In the four people group, my main works are **Mechanical design** and **parts of Arduino code establishing**. Finally, we get the fourth place among 20 teams.

2019.10 - 2021.08

Join Eurobot competition

Topic: Sail the world - Automated robot for multi-tasks

Because of COVID-19, the competition used same topic for two years. We also built six different types of robot for two generations. My main contributions in first year are **ROS finite-state machine establishing** and **STM32 firmware coding**. In the second year, I developed and studied **Navigation** of robot in ROS.

0 2021.08 - 2021.12

Join Undergraduate Research competition

Topic: System integration and development of robotic arm in mobile robot

Our main purpose in the project is to construct an mobile robot with high degrees of freedom and mobility, so we chose **SCARA** as the type of manipulator, and **three mecanum Wheels with independent control** as the chassis. We built this robot from scratch, and my main contributions included **mechanical design and firmware coding for the end actuator of SCARA**, **GUI and state machine code in ROS**.

Course Expectation

- O Learn the main theory of ICP and SLAM
- O Train my ability of coding
- O Contact with state-of-art SDC technology